spn.sr 2014-07-03

# Privacy Policy | Revenue.com

## Privacy Policy

(Last updated 09/13/13)

Protecting your private information is very important to the Revenue.com team. This Privacy Policy describes how Revenue.com will treat the information it collects from you when you visit and use any website associated with Virurl, Inc (DBA "Revenue.com"). Revenue.com is committed to respecting the privacy rights and concerns of its users. By visiting Revenue.com, you consent to the terms and conditions as set forth in this Privacy Policy. For any additional information, questions, or concerns, you may email support@revenue.com for additional information.

### Information and collection of use

When you register your information through Revenue.com or visit a Revenue.com page, Revenue.com collects personal information from you. Revenue.com may, at its sole discretion, combine any information you provide with other personal information that it obtains from business partners and other companies. With your registration, you provide us with personal information such as your name and email address, and you are not anonymous to Revenue.com. Further, Revenue.com automatically receives information from your computer in addition to the information that you provide, such as your IP address, Revenue.com cookie information, software and hardware information, and the pages you visit. Revenue.com may, at its discretion, use this information for any purpose, including but not limited to: customizing the content that you see on Revenue.com, fulfilling your requests for products and services, improving our services, contacting you, and/or conducting our own research. You may customize your notification settings on your Revenue.com account page.

### Information Sharing

Revenue.com commits to its users that it will not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other non-affiliated companies or persons except to provide any product or service you request and upon your permission. Notwithstanding the foregoing, however, Revenue.com will provide your information when legally required to do so pursuant to a subpoena, court order, or other legal process including to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against a legal claim. If Revenue.com becomes involved in a merger, acquisition or sale of all or some of its assets, Revenue.com will provide you with notice before any personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Access to your Computer

Cookies are small bits of electronic information that a website sends to a visitor's browser and are stored on the visitor's hard drive. Like many websites, Revenue.com may set and access cookies on your computer to provide information that is targeted to you. Revenue.com uses these cookies in connection with Revenue.com products and services. The information that Revenue.com accesses through these cookies is commonly made available and collected by web browsers and servers. This information includes, but is not limited to: language preference, browser type, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Revenue.com uses this information to understand how you use this website.

### Contents of Posted Items

Any item that you post directly on Revenue.com, including any text, image, photo, video, and/or audio is stored and maintained on the Revenue.com servers in order to publish such item(s) and provide service to our users. Your submitted conduct will be associated with your account. When you post directly to Revenue.com, you are agreeing that this information is not copyrighted, trademarked, or otherwise protected by anyone other than you. You are also indicating that you have permission to post such item(s).

### Security and Confidentiality

Revenue.com limits access to your personal information to employees who we believe reasonably need access to this information to provide products or services to you or to otherwise do their jobs. Such employees are bound by confidentiality obligations, and, if they fail to meet these obligations, may be subject to discipline and criminal prosecution.

### Third Party Sites

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Revenue.com website and related services. Revenue.com exercises no control over the sites to which our service links. You should know that these other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer and may collect data or solicit personal information from you. Revenue.com encourages you to read the privacy policies of any third-party site you visit. Revenue.com is not liable for the wrongful use or disclosure of your personally identifying information by any third party. Indeed, it is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personal information.

### Data Integrity

Revenue.com processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Revenue.com reviews its data collection, storage, and processing practices from time to time to ensure that Revenue.com only collects, stores, and process the necessary personal information to provide and/or improve its services. Revenue.com takes reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is accurate, complete, and current, but it depends on its users to update and/or correct their personal information as appropriate.

### This Policy

Revenue.com may update or change this policy at anytime and at its sole discretion. Revenue.com encourages users to check this page frequently for any changes to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such a change. For all inquiries related to this Privacy Policy, please email privacy@revenue.com.
